https://www.wadecollectorsclub.co.uk/terms-and-conditions-privacy/

Expand/collapse navigation
Home & Latest News & Products12 Days Of ChristmasWade Christmas Bonanza 2020 Bonanza Whimsie OffersChristmas Bonanza Bran Draw, Lucky Dip and More EventsLatest Wade OffersWade Collectors Club FacebookWade Whimsieland Christmas CrackersWade Christmas CollectablesWade Whimsie Day BeesSave & Collect Loyalty ProgrammeNew Thelwell WhimsiesWade Join Club - News & Archive Collectors Club MembershipWade Articles & Features About UsA Bit of a Whimsie By Carole MurdockA Family of PotteriesA Mark of British Pottery HistoryChown & Schooley - An Amazing Tale by Carole MurdockGoodbye To The Wade Collectors MeetI'm A Wade Collector by Mike Posgay and Ian WarnerIris Wade Carryer - A Legend in Her TimeMemories in Porcelain by Carole MurdockMy Wade HavenNat West Pigs – A Brief HistoryNat West Pigs : Did You Know?Ready! Set! Collect! by Carole MurdockRed Rose Tea WhimsiesSir George WadeSpotlight on Angela GoodsellSpotlight on Dee LeBlancSpotlight on The Myszkowski’sTime For Tea - TetleyWade-Ing A Family Affair by Carole MurdockWade Fest USA 2016Wade Flower Jugs - By Ian Warner and Mike PosgayWade Club Members Only/Renewals Wade House Grey Ant ExclusiveThe Wade House Facebook Group - Club Members Only2020 Happy Family Membership Pieces2019 Happy Family Membership Pieces2018 Pottery Pets Membership Pieces2017 Pottery Pets Memberhsip Pieces2016 Happy Family Membership Pieces2015 Happy Family Membership Pieces2014 Membership Pieces2013 Membership Pieces2012 Membership PiecesWade Bracelet CharmsShop For Collectables To Main ShopWade Club Membership Pieces 2019 - Club Members Only - Renew MembershipWade Club Membership Pieces 2018 - Club Members Only - Renew MembershipClub Members Only - Renew MembershipBeswick SnowmenBetty Boop Alphabet LettersDisney Britto Mini FiguresDisney Magical MomentsGingie Bear GiftsHagen-Renaker Made in the USAJoin Wade Collectors ClubNao PorcelainNew Baby BoopPeanuts - SnoopyNew Betty BoopSpecial WhimsiesWade Whimsie DayPrototypes - SamplesSale - Special Offer ItemsSeasonal GiftsValentine GiftsVintage Wade CollectablesWade Bran Draw TicketsWhimsie-Nation WhimsiesAbout us Legal NoticeOur teamDirectionsBusiness HoursCelebration Cake ToppersContact UsBetty Boop News & Shop 2020 Betty Boop CatalogueBetty Boop ShopBetty Boop Christmas GiftsGingie BearC&S Archive C&S Archive Articles & Features About UsBetty BoopCelebrating 60 Years of Wade WhimsiesCeramic Wall PlaquesC&S AwardChristmas Bonanza 2016 ReviewFaust Lang – A Short BiographyIris Carryer The Early YearsJessie Van HallenPennies or PorcelainSir George WadeSnow White & The Seven DwarfsThe Wade Hagen-Renaker ConnectionWade a Good Investment?Wade Made in EnglandWade Manchester PotteryWade Old and NewWade WhimblesWade Whimsies - A Short HistoryWade WhoppasWhimsie-Nation ArchiveWilliam Harper - A Short BiographyLinksTerms and Conditions - PrivacyWade Fairs - Events - Dates Wade Summer Open DayWade Christmas Bonanza
Home & Latest News & Products12 Days Of ChristmasWade Christmas Bonanza 2020Latest Wade OffersWade Collectors Club FacebookWade Whimsieland Christmas CrackersWade Christmas CollectablesWade Whimsie Day BeesSave & Collect Loyalty ProgrammeNew Thelwell WhimsiesWade Join Club - News & ArchiveWade Club Members Only/RenewalsWade Bracelet CharmsShop For CollectablesAbout usCelebration Cake ToppersContact UsBetty Boop News & ShopGingie BearC&S ArchiveLinksTerms and Conditions - PrivacyWade Fairs - Events - Dates
Terms and Conditions
The information contained in this website is for general information purposes only. The information is provided by the Wade Collectors Club Ltd and while we endeavour to keep the information up to
date and correct, we make no representations or warranties of any kind, express or implied, about the completeness, accuracy, reliability, suitability or availability with respect to the website or
the information, products, services, or related graphics contained on the website for any purpose. Any reliance you place on such information is therefore strictly at your own risk.
In no event will we be liable for any loss or damage including without limitation, indirect or consequential loss or damage, or any loss or damage whatsoever arising from loss of data or profits
arising out of, or in connection with, the use of this website.
Through this website you are able to link to other websites which are not under the control of the Wade Collectors Club Ltd. We have no control over the nature, content and availability of those
sites. The inclusion of any links does not necessarily imply a recommendation or endorse the views expressed within them.
Every effort is made to keep the website up and running smoothly. However, the Wade Collectors Club Ltd takes no responsibility for, and will not be liable for, the website being temporarily
unavailable due to technical issues beyond our control.
Privacy Policy
Your Consent
By using our site, you consent to our web site privacy
policy.
1. Introduction
Wade
Collectors Club takes your privacy very seriously. This privacy policy describes how and why we obtain, store and process data which can identify you. We may update this policy from time to time and
will indicate on the website when changes have been made.
2. We never disclose any information or data to third parties.
If you place and order from our website the
information you provide will never be used for any other purpose than the order placed. If you sign up for our newletter the information provided will only be used for our newsletter
purposes.
3. Security
Keeping
information about you secure is very important to us and our site wadecollectorsclub.co.uk is encrypted using SSL. However, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be totally
secure. As a result, whilst we strive to protect your personal information, we cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information which you send to us, and you do so at your own risk.
4. Accessing and updating your personal information
We will
always let you have a copy of personal information we have about you, should you request it, and you may correct it if you wish.
5. Questions?
If you
have any questions relating to this Privacy Policy or how we use the personal information we have about you, please contact club@wadecollectorsclub.co.uk
Check out What's New
Enter Now!
Join The Wade Collectors Club
Betty Boop Seasonal
Christmas Bonanza 2020
2020 Wade Christmas Crackers
Thelwell Whimsies
Wade Collectors
Club Membership Pieces 2020
Join The Wade Club Here
Betty Boop Catalogue
Download Catalogue here
Beswick Snowman Collection
Go Shopping In Our Collectors Gift Shop
Come and visit
C&S @ The Wade Collectors Club
Victorian Business Centre,
Ford Lane, Ford, Arundel,
West Sussex, BN18 0EF
Tel: +44 (0) 7767 475944 or +44 (0) 1243 555371
Our business hours
Monday - Friday10:00 - 16:00Outside of business hours you can contact us by email csdirect@compuserve.com or club@wadecollectorsclub.co.uk or leave a message on + 44 (0) 7767 475944 or +44 (0) 1243 555371
Print
|
Sitemap
Recommend this page
© Wade Collectors Club Ltd - Betty Boop © 2020 King Features Syndicate, Inc./Fleischer Studios, Inc. TM Hearts Holdings, Inc./Fleischer Studios Inc Gingie Bear © C&S Collectables Direct -
Victorian Business Centre, Ford Lane, Arundel, West Sussex, England, BN18 0EF Registered in England 6012777 Vat # GB 913 5700 44 © 1992 - 2020 Wade Collectors Club Ltd - No part of this website may
be reproduced in any form without written consent from The Wade Collectors Club Ltd - Refund policy. If you for any reason you are not happy with your purchase, you may return it for a replacement or
refund. Call us on 01243 555371 or email csdirect@compuserve.com We do not share any information with third parties.
Web ViewMobile View
Logout |
Edit page
0
